Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Richard V. Szary, head of Manuscripts and Archives, records, 1991-2006; Accession 2007-A-134
  - University Archives
    - Archives 300
      - Media
        - Film storage procedures, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Media processing manual, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Notes and lists, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Plans and progress reports, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Records management, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Records transfer instructions, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Revitalization, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Secretary's office, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Staff photograph, 2000 February (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Tercentennial Office, 2000 April (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Tercentennial Steering Committee and website, 2000 April (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - University Archives Working Group, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - University Records Survey Final Report (NHPRC grant), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Weekly reports, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 34 - 35)
    - Collections Management
      - Access
        - Access and use: University policy, 1956-2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Management of restrictions, 1980-2000 (Box 1, Folder 37 - 39)
        - Policies: other universities, circa 1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
        - Policies: pending, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 41)
        - Requests to access restricted material, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 44)
        - Requests to access restricted material: pending, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      - Accession database: WordPerfect, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Accession folder inventory, 1996 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Accession records
        - Problems by accession number, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 48)
        - Problems by YRG, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Accessioning checklists, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 50 - 51)
      - Beinecke transfers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Collection management system
        - 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 53)
        - 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
        - A/V database, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 55)
        - CMS redesign, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
        - Database, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 57)
        - Locator integration, circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
        - Locator reconciliation, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Office of origin requests, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - Location register
        - 1988 Feb 5 (Box 1, Folder 61)
        - 1988 Oct 25 (Box 1, Folder 62)
        - 1991 Jul 5 (Box 1, Folder 63)
        - 1992 Jul 8 (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - RLIN quarterly accession lists, 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 65 - 67)
      - RU (record unit) assignment, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Vault lists from locator database, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Vault list: Archives, 1991 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Committees and advisory groups
      - Archives Committee
        - prior to FY 1991-1992, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - FY1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Corporation meetings, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Tercentennial
      - History and Archives subcommittee
        - Budget planning, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - Planning, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 75)
        - Meeting and final report, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - Publications committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - Planning Committee Report, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - University Archives, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - University History and Archives Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Forms of material
      - Computer files
      - Architecture
        - Architectural drawings: scanning, 1989, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 82)
        - Architectural plans and drawings, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 83)
        - Background information, circa 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 84)
        - Buildings and Grounds: general, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 85)
        - Facilities IDs, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 86)
        - Facility planning: building timeline, circa 1993 (Box 2, Folder 87)
        - Facilities planning: pre-1997, 1980-1993 (Box 2, Folder 88)
        - Facilities planning: 1997-, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 89)
        - Finding aids, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 90)
        - General information, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 91)
        - Graduate and professional schools, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 92)
        - Guide documentation, 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 93)
        - Microfilm: Architecture and Engineering, circa 1991 (Box 2, Folder 94)
        - Processing: pre-1997, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 95)
        - Records management, 1989-2000 (Box 2, Folder 97)
        - RU history, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 98)
        - Sample schedules, circa 1998 (Box 2, Folder 99)
        - Scanning project
          - Frame sequences, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 100)
          - NMI bid, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 101)
          - Pilot, budget, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 102)
      - Corporation records
        - Digitizing corporation records, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 103)
        - Notes, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      - Dissertations and theses
        - Electronic, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 105)
        - Loan policies, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 106)
        - Policies and procedures, 1986-1999 (Box 2, Folder 107)
        - ProQuest, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 108)
        - UMI scanning, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 109)
      - Computer files
        - Canadian symposium, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 110)
        - Digital preservation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 111)
        - ERA, circa 2004 (Box 2, Folder 112)
        - Electronic lists, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 113)
        - Electronic research, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 114)
        - NHPRC grant, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 115)
        - Notes, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 116)
        - Project, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 117)
      - Media
        - Assessment project, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 118)
        - Assessment of holdings, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 119)
        - Holdings: audio recordings, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 120)
        - Visual Resources Archivist proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 121)
        - Projects: general, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 122)
        - Audio-Visual
          - AV database development, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 123)
          - AV at School of Architecture, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 124)
          - Film
            - Films transferred from Yale Film Study Center, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 125)
            - Films at athletics, 1987, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 126)
            - Films at non-Yale repositories, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 127)
            - Moving images, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 128)
            - Moving images, audio, graphics, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 129)
          - Preservation
            - General information, circa 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 130)
            - Vendors, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 131)
          - Procedures
            - General information, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 132)
            - Licensing, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 133)
            - Licensing contracts, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 134)
            - Library Storage Facility guidelines, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 135)
          - Projects
            - Devane Lecture Series, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 136)
            - York St. survey results, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 139 - 140)
          - Photographs
            - FYI (Find Yale Images) database development, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 141)
            - FYI image rescan list, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 142)
            - Procedures:general, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 143)
            - Projects
            - YPC Pictures, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 148)
      - Microfilming
        - Archives microfilming, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 149)
        - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 150)
        - Yale College records, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 151)
        - Yale Daily News, circa 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 152)
        - HM 17: Faculty judgments, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 153)
        - HM 49: Corporation records, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 154)
        - HM 50: Prudential Committee records, circa 1990 (Box 3, Folder 155)
        - HM 214: President's reports, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 156)
        - HM 216: Board of Permanent Officers Minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 157)
        - HM 217: Faculty meeting minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 158)
      - Publications
        - Assessment, 1988-2000 (Box 3, Folder 159)
        - Projects: class albums, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 160)
        - Web sites, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 161)
        - Yale Alumni Magazine indexing, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 162)
        - Yale Daily News, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 163)
      - Scrapbooks, circa 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 164 - 165)
      - Student papers, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 166)
      - Student records, 1981-1992 (Box 3, Folder 167)
      - Yale objects, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Intellectual access
      - Administrative history
        - Yale University, circa 1999 (Box 3, Folder 169)
        - Yale University Library, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 170)
        - Manual, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 171)
      - Archives Authority, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 172)
      - Arrangement and description: University Archives processing priorities, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 173)
      - Cataloging, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 174)
      - Catalog records, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 175)
      - Descriptive program, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 176)
      - Descriptive standards, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 177)
      - Information architecture, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 178)
      - Finding aids, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 179)
      - MARC-AMC records, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 180)
      - Problems and issues, 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 181)
      - Presentation to staff on new structure (RU), 1994 October 13 (Box 4, Folder 182)
      - Processing needs, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 183)
      - Record unit master lists, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 184)
      - Retrospective description project, phase 1, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 185)
      - RLIN
        - Accessions
          - Not entered, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 186)
          - Questions pending, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 187)
          - Worksheet problems, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 188)
          - YRG accessions 87-A problems, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 189)
        - Records, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 190)
      - Yale Record Groups
        - Background, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 191)
        - Checklist, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 192)
        - Classes for review by archivists, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 193)
        - Old lists, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 194)
        - Reconcile YRG/RU/etc., 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 196)
        - Record unit tracking record, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 197)
        - Restructuring, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Offices
      - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 199)
      - Alumni Records, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 200)
      - Anthropology, Department of, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - Architecture, School of, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 202)
      - Art, School of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 203)
      - Art, School of: thesis work, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 204)
      - Astronomy, Department of, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 205)
      - Athletics, 1981, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 206 - 207)
      - Bingham Oceanographic, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 208)
      - Biology (FAS), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 209)
      - Bureau of Highway Traffic, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 210)
      - Chicano and Asian American Cultural Center at Yale, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 211)
      - Council of Masters, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 212)
      - Council on Russian and East European Studies, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 213)
      - Economics (FAS), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 214)
      - Engineering, School of, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 215)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 216)
      - Facilities, 1989, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 217)
      - Foreign Students and Scholars, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 218)
      - Forestry, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 219)
      - General Counsel: Justice Department Investigation, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 220 - 221)
      - Graduate School, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 222)
      - Historical Medical, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 223)
      - History Department, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 224)
      - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (ISPS), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 225)
      - International Security Studies (ISS), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 226)
      - Law School, Yale, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 227)
      - Medical School, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 228)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1991 (Box 4, Folder 229)
      - Music, School of, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 230)
      - Nursing, School of, 1982, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 231 - 232)
      - Organization and Management, School of, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 233)
      - Physics, Department of, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 234)
      - Political Science, Department of, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 235)
      - Provost, circa 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 236 - 237)
      - Public Affairs, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 238)
      - Purchasing, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 239)
      - Religious ministries, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 240)
      - Residential colleges, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 241)
      - Residential colleges: dean's assistants, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 242)
      - Residential College Seminar, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 243)
      - Secretary, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 244)
      - Southern Africa Research Program, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 245)
      - Student Financial and Administrative Services, circa 1995 (Box 4, Folder 246)
      - Student organizations
        - General, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 247)
        - Whiffenpoofs, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 248 - 249)
      - Summer and Special Programs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 250)
      - Undergraduate Financial Aid, 1991, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 251 - 252)
      - University Auditing, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 253)
      - WYBC, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 254)
      - Yale Art Gallery, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 255)
      - Yale-China Association, 1989-1995 (Box 4, Folder 256)
      - Yale Club of New York, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 257)
      - Yale College
        - Class of 1953, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 258)
        - Dean's Office, 1979, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 259 - 260)
        - History, the Arts and Letters, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 261)
      - Yale Daily News, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 262)
      - Yale Dramat, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 263)
      - Yale University Films, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 264)
      - Yale University Library
        - Manuscripts and Archives: Livelink, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 265)
        - Systems Office, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 266)
        - Thomas More Project, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 267)
      - Yale University Press, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Plans and reports
      - Annual reports
        - 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 269)
        - Excerpts from Manuscripts and Archives report, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 270)
        - 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 271 - 274)
      - Annual statistics, 1989-1992, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 275 - 276)
      - Archives plans, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 277)
      - Cost recovery, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 278)
      - Five year plan, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 279)
      - Goals and activities, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 280 - 281)
      - Guide to services, 1991, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 282 - 283)
      - Library relationship, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 284)
      - Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 285)
      - Notes and lists, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 286)
      - Personnel and staffing, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 287)
      - Potential projects, plans, 1988-1995 (Box 5, Folder 288)
      - Presentation to MPSA, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 289)
      - Program planning, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 290)
      - Progress reports, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 291 - 292)
      - Sources, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 293)
      - Students, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 294)
      - Support, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Policies and procedures
      - Accessioning procedures, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 296)
      - Acknowledgment procedures, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 297)
      - Archives program, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 298)
      - Collection development statement of responsibilities, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 299)
      - Document retention policy, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 300)
      - Policies and procedures forms, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 301)
      - Guide to Services, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 302)
      - Masters
        - Core statement, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 303)
        - Collection policy, 1980, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 304)
        - Minimum level processing, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 305)
        - Record appraisal guidelines, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 306)
        - Archival interests, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 307)
        - Accession worksheet, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 308)
        - Accessioning policies and procedures, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 309)
        - For recon project, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 310)
      - Office procedures manual, revision, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 311)
      - Records Transfer Procedures, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 312)
      - Request for Transfer of Records, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 313)
      - Research Use of the Yale University Archives, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 314)
      - Schedule of Archival Services, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Projects
      - Brewster project, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 316)
      - Historical databases
        - Book of Numbers, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 317)
        - Historical Register
          - AAR, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 318)
          - Background and notes, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 319)
          - Conversion
            - PacData Info, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 320)
            - RFPs and bids, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 321)
          - Editing: PacData, circa 1999 (Box 5, Folder 322)
          - General, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 323)
      - Historical resources
        - Buildings and Grounds, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 324)
        - Encyclopedia, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 325)
        - New York Times index, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 326 - 327)
      - Nepal film, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 328)
      - OCSF (Off Campus Shelving Facility), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 329)
      - Ongoing YRG/RU cleanup, 1987-1997 (Box 5, Folder 330)
      - Oral History Program, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 331)
      - SPIRES, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 332)
      - SPIRES-CMS, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 333)
      - YEP (Yale Encyclopedia Program), 2004 (Box 5, Folder 334)
      - Yale History web site, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Yale History web site: reference and historical notes from YRG files, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - Records management
      - Computer files
      - Archives program, 1980-1996 (Box 5, Folder 337)
      - Livelink implementation: Secretary's Office, circa 2001 (Box 5, Folder 338)
      - MIF (Management Issues Forum) Expo, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - Manuscripts and Archives
    - Mailbox inventory, computer file (XML)
    - Notes
      - 1989 (Box 6, Folder 340)
      - 1991 (Box 6, Folder 341)
      - Monthly Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 342)
      - Daily Notes, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 343 - 344)
      - 1993 (Box 6, Folder 345)
      - 1993 Jan (Box 6, Folder 346)
      - 1993 Jul (Box 6, Folder 347)
      - 1994 Jan (Box 6, Folder 348)
      - 1994 Mar (Box 6, Folder 349)
      - 1994 Apr (Box 6, Folder 350)
      - 1994 May (Box 6, Folder 351)
      - 1994 Jun (Box 6, Folder 352)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 353)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 354)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 355)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 356)
      - 1995 Jul-1996 Apr (Box 6, Folder 357)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 358)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 359)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 360)
      - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - Administration
      - Administration group, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 380)
      - Reporting and Statistics, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 381)
      - Statistics, 1987-1995 (Box 6, Folder 382)
      - Annual reports
        - 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 383)
        - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 384)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 385)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 386)
        - 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 387)
        - Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 388)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 389)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 390)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 391)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 392)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 393)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 394)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 395)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 396)
      - MSSA Organization charts and phone lists, 1987-1992 (Box 6, Folder 397)
      - Departmental Organization, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 398 - 399)
      - MSSA Restructuring, 1992 June - September (Box 7, Folder 400)
      - Departmental Audit, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 401)
      - Reference and Reader Services Staffing, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 402)
      - Plans, projects, progress, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 403)
      - Planning - Departmental, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 404)
      - Departmental Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 405)
      - Action Planning
        - 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 406)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 407)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 408)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 409)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 410)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 411)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 412)
      - Topics for staff meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 413)
      - Departmental staff meetings
        - 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 414)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 415)
        - 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 416)
        - 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 417)
        - 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 418)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 419)
      - Staff procedures - new and departing staff, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 420)
      - Departmental Office Procedures, 1989-1997 (Box 7, Folder 421)
      - Staff: standards of conduct, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 422)
      - Manuscripts and Archives New Staff Orientation, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 423)
      - New staff orientation, 1993 December (Box 7, Folder 424)
      - Mission statements, 1983-1995 (Box 7, Folder 425)
      - Programmatic emphasis, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 426)
      - Planning: baseline of current activities, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 427)
      - Statements of priorities, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 428)
    - Facilities
      - 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 429)
      - Stats, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 430)
      - Safety and incidents, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 431)
      - Security - Keys, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 432)
      - Back area, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 433)
      - Cowles Reference Center - renovation, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 434)
      - Dissertation Room, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 435)
      - HGS, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 436)
      - LSF planning and preparation, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 437)
      - Memorabilia Room - Exhibit cases - security, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 438)
      - Meyer-Weiker, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 439)
      - Multi-purpose room, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 440)
      - Processing Room - renovation, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 441)
      - 149 York, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 442)
      - York Street, 1991-1994 (Box 7, Folder 443)
      - York St. - Alumni Records, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 444)
      - SML 69, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - Connections
      - Task Force, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 446)
      - Pub programs - Info requests, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 447)
      - Information requests and visitors, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 448)
      - Visitors
        - Information, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 449)
      - American Institute of Physics, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 451)
      - Brochure - Departmental, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 452)
      - Web site, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 453 - 454)
      - Requests for information, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 455)
      - Events, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 456)
      - Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 457)
      - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA) Assembly, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 458)
      - Courses - Intellectual History of the American College, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 459)
      - Connecticut Committee for the Preservation of Architectural Records (COPAR), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 460)
      - Library Orientation Tours, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 461)